http://www.fortunebaby.com/privacypolicy.html

Privacy policy
FortuneBaby.comFortune Baby Web site is intended for use by users and prospective users of Fortune Baby services and products.HomeStart Gender PredictorReviewsMy ResultsFree Gifts
Home » Predictors » Proven » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This statement discloses the privacy practices of
www.fortunebaby.com
FortuneBaby's Web site is intended for use by users and prospective users of
FortuneBaby's services and products. FortuneBaby.com values your confidence and
has maintained this policy to demonstrate our commitment to protect all
information, which we obtain through our Web site. This Privacy Policy may be
modified if legal requirements are changed, Any changes to this Privacy Policy
will be posted on the Web Site. All information submitted through the Web Site
is subject to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not govern
FortuneBaby.com collection or use of data through channels other than this Web
Site.
If you have any questions about the privacy practices of this site or the
privacy statement, please send correspondence to email
info@fortunebaby.com.
I. Confidentiality Policy
Personal contact information (such as name, title, address, telephone number
and email address), demographic information (such as country and zip code) and
your purchase history are information considered to be private and confidential.
Such information collected through this site will, accordingly, be stored in a
secured location, accessible only by designated staff for purposes provided for
and will be purged permanently from the data base once the service period is
legally expired.
Information sharing
Fortune Baby only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of FortuneBaby in the following limited circumstances:
We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Fortune Baby, its users or the public as required or permitted by law
II. Information Release Policy
All voluntarily submitted information will be used for FortuneBaby.com
products and services only and will not be sold or leased to third party.
FortuneBaby.com do not maintain computerized customer list and will not send
unsolicited email.
Also, in order to optimize the content on the site, we ask that visitors
register to receive certain requested content. Once a visitor completes the
registration process, they will not need to register at this site again. The
registration process utilizes a cookie placed in the registrants browser solely
for the purpose of recognizing that visitor as a registrant and bypassing any
future registration processes. Registrants whose browsers do not accept cookies
will need to re-enter their confirmation code or re-register for certain
content. FortuneBaby.com may follow-up with registered visitors via email or
phone.
III. Information Tracking Policy
Our web site do not track or collect any identifiable information of the
visitors such as names, addresses or other particular information related to a
home server. However, this site compiles statistics to show the daily number of
visitors, daily requests received by this site and which geographical area these
requests came from. This information is used only for internal purpose to better
our service to the public and will be securely safeguarded.
IV. Security Safeguards Policy
Data security is important to our business. FortuneBaby.com takes steps,
including physical, managerial and technical safeguards, to protect any
information about Web site users. User data, including password files, are
protected by industry-standard firewall technologies and may be accessed only by
authorized personnel.
Please remember that you are also responsible for the security of our site.
Any confirmation code or password to access our site should never be shared with
anyone and should be changed frequently. After visiting a protected area, you
should exit your browser to prevent unauthorized entry. This privacy policy
applies only to FortuneBaby.com Web site; when visiting other sites, which may
be linked to our site, carefully review the applicable privacy policies before
revealing any personal or sensitive information. As there is no absolute
security on the Internet, we cannot warrant the security of any information you
provide to us, and you provide such information at your own risk.
If you did not find the answer to your question, please visit our Contact Us section.
What's New?Special OffersFAQGender PredictorsGender Predictor1-Year Gender Selection4-Year Gender Selection
Share it
Customer feedback"Thanks for the awesome result! I used your online baby gender predictor and the result was a Boy. Few weeks later, our scan confirmed that we are having a baby Boy. We are excited and very happy! I will recommend your site to everyone.""A GREAT BIG THANK YOU! We are having a girl as you predicted when I requested a four year gender selection test. We are so excited as we have 2 boys and they are looking forward to the arrival of a beautiful baby sister to love and cherish. Your gender predictor was also correct for my second child." read more...
Fortune Baby Gender Predictor ReviewsThousands of happy moms around the world successfully used Fortunebaby gender prediction test.
We are delighted to share their gender prediction reviews about their experience with Fortune Baby.I just wanted to say thank you. My husband and I used your gender prediction test and was told that I would be having a boy. Everyone told me because of the way I was carrying and the fact I am Sick all the time that I would be having a girl. Well we just had our ultrasound and found out it's a BOY! We are so happy. Now we will have two BOYS! I can't believe it worked!!! Thank you again!I took your gender prediction test in July 2009, and it came up with GIRL. I was a bit skeptical, and took a urine based test that clearly showed BOY. They will not tell you the gender on ultrasounds in our town, so I had to wait until November to find out, and it turns out I should have just gone on Fortune Baby's results after all--we had a girl! Thanks! I passed on my daughters details to find out the gender of her baby and you said she was having a girl. On Wednesday of this week she went for her 21 week scan at the hospital, and yes, she is having a little girl. Thank you for such an accurate predication! I will pass on this site to my friends daughter who is also pregnant.I just wanted to let you know that you were right again! I did a test on my cousin and you guys predicted that she was having a boy she went for her sonogram and sure enough she is. I also did a test for myself but I won't know until the end of next month but I will keep you guys posted. Thanks!!!!!! YOU GUYS ARE GREAT!!!!!!!!!START FORTUNE BABY GENDER PREDICTOR TEST | READ ALL REVIEWS
Gender Predictors:Calendars: View allCalculators:Is it a boy or a girl testTake gender predictor quizList of old wives talesAncient chinese gender chartPregnancy calendarOvulation calendarWeek by week pregnancy calendarChinese Pregnancy CalendarPregnancy due date calculatorPregnancy Weight Gain CalculatorOvulation CalculatorPregnancy TickersPregnancy Early Signs: Quiz | ListPregnancy Articles View allPregnancy ProblemsMissed Menstrual PeriodHeartburn during pregnancyMorning SicknessFrequent Urination during PregnancyPregnancy ConstipationPregnancy StagesPregnancy PicturesPregnancy Guide | First PregnancyExercise during pregnancySleep during pregnancyPregnancy dietLabor and DeliverySex during pregnancyTeenage pregnancyFetal Development 1st | 2nd | 3rdPregnancy complicationsPregnancy bleedingPregnancy back painCramps during pregnancySearch
Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Help | Contact© 1997 - 2020 Fortune Baby™ » Privacy policy
